Fox Theater Memories Project Records, 1883-2011 (bulk 1925-2008)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
Fox Theater Memories Project Records, 1883-2011 (bulk 1925-2008)
MS 560
Buehler, Bill.
The Fox Theater Memories Project Records (1883-2011) contains historical research files, oral history interviews, and documented restoration efforts of the Fox Theater gathered by the Fox Theater Memories Project.
9.6 linear feet
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL: http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/ E-Mail: LBRY-askspcoll@email.arizona.edu
Restrictions
There are no restrictions on this collection.
Historical Note
The Fox Tucson Theater began its life as a 1,300-seat movie palace on April 11th, 1930. For years it delighted Tucsonans with the finest Hollywood fare, including premieres and visits from stars. Also of note was the Mickey Mouse Club, an organized outlet for Tucson's kids to spend time at the theater to watch films, participate in contests, as well as other activities. The theater closed in 1974, remaining largely intact; the business records of the theater were thrown out. During the theater's closure, many homeless people found refuge inside the abandoned building.
In 1999, Tucson citizens formed the Fox Tucson Theatre Foundation, led by Herb Stratford who would later manage the theater's operation from 2006 to 2008. As a non-profit corporation, the foundation's mission was to purchase, renovate, and restore the theater to its original grandeur. It is the only Southwest art deco theater known to exist, and in April 2004 was designated a National Landmark. The theater reopened in 2005 as a fully functioning movie palace and performing arts facility.
The Fox Theater Memories Project was part of the foundation's efforts, managed by Bill Buehler, to preserve Tucson's cultural heritage, having done extensive research on the history of the theater while the restoration was taking place. This project utilized several volunteers to help research materials, and many interviews with those that experienced the Fox Theater in its heyday were conducted.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into 4 series.
Series I: Historical files, 1929-2011 (bulk 1929-1974)
Series II: Subject files, 1883-2004 (bulk 1930-1945)
Series III: Oral History files, 1915-2006
Series IV: Oral History media, 2001-2008
Scope and Content Note
Records 1883-2011: This collection documents the Fox Theater as it was through press clipping copies, research project files, logs, oral history interviews as well as documented restoration efforts, all collected by volunteers of the Fox Theater Memories Project. Most materials are on copied or printed paper, but there are also newspaper clippings, photographs, written notes, VHS tapes, cassette tapes, and Mini DV tapes. Original business records for the theater are unavailable, as they were disposed of in the 1960s.
Access Terms
Arizona Film Commission.
Fox Tucson Theatre Foundation.
Fox Theater (Tucson, Ariz.)
Mickey Mouse Club.
Movie ads of the past.
Stratford, Herb.
Container List
- Series I: Historical files, 1929-2011; (bulk 1929-1974)
  Contains historical research files collected and maintained by various volunteers. Files include press clipping copies from microfilm of news, events, and films pertaining to the Fox Theater in chronological order. Included is a complete history of all the films shown at the Fox Theater. Many files include notes written on the back of them. Some files serve as the basis of or are referenced to by many oral history interviews that were conducted.
  - Fox News, March 2, 1929-December 31, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Fox Special Films, August 16, 1929-September 1, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Fox Opening News, January 18, 1930-December 28, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Fox Onstage Live Events (1 of 3), March 3, 1930-June 7, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Fox Onstage Live Events (2 of 3), March 3, 1930-June 7, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Fox Onstage Live Events (3 of 3), March 3, 1930-June 7, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Fox News, Arizona Wildcat, April 4, 1930-March 8, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Fox Chronology, April 11, 1930-June 18, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Opening Night Film, May 3, 1930, September 23, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Fox Film Premieres, October 18, 1930-February 16, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Alphabetized List of Movies at Fox, 1930-1934 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Fox Film Titles List (1 of 2), 1930-1974 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Fox Film Titles List (2 of 2), 1930-1974 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Fox Films, January 1, 1930-June 30, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Fox Films, July 1, 1930-December 31, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Fox News, January 3, 1930-December 31, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Fox Mickey Mouse Club, May 29, 1930-December 26, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Fox Films, January 1, 1931-June 30, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Fox Films, July 1, 1931-December 31, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Fox News, January 4, 1931-December 27, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Fox Mickey Mouse Club, January 7, 1931-December 31, 1931 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Fox Films, January 1, 1932-June 30, 1932 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Fox Films, July 1, 1932-December 31, 1932 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Fox News, January 2, 1932-December 31, 1932 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Fox Mickey Mouse Club, January 13, 1932-December 24, 1932 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Fox Griffith Dance Team, September 28, 1932-July 5, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Fox Films, January 2, 1933-June 29, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Fox Films, July 1, 1933-December 31, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Fox News, January 12, 1933-December 27, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Fox Mickey Mouse Club, January 7, 1933-December 30, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Fox Films, January 1, 1934-June 30, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Fox Films, July 1, 1934-December 31, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Fox News, January 12, 1934-December 31, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Fox Mickey Mouse Club, January 6, 1934-December 29, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Fox Films, January 1, 1935-June 30, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Fox Films, July 2, 1935-December 31, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Fox News, January 13, 1935-December 29, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Fox Mickey Mouse Club, January 5, 1935-December 29, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Alphabetized List of Movies at Fox, 1935-1939 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Fox Films, January 2, 1936-June 30, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Fox Films, July 1, 1936-December 31, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Fox News, February 16, 1936-October 2, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Fox Mickey Mouse Club, January 18, 1936-December 26, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Fox Films, January 1, 1937-June 30, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Fox Films, July 1, 1937-December 31, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Fox News, January 8, 1937-December 22, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Fox Mickey Mouse Club, January 2, 1937-December 24, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Fox Films, January 1, 1938-June 30, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Fox Films, July 1, 1938-December 31, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Fox News, January 15, 1938-December 30, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Fox Mickey Mouse Club, January 8, 1938-December 31, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Fox Films, January 1, 1939-June 29, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Fox Films, July 2, 1939-December 31, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Fox News, January 28, 1939-December 30, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Fox Mickey Mouse Club, January 7, 1939-December 30, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Fox Films, January 1, 1940-December 31, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Fox News, January 5, 1940-December 19, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Fox Mickey Mouse Club, January 6, 1940-December 21, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Fox Films, January 5, 1941-December 31, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Fox News, January 1, 1941-December 28, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Fox Mickey Mouse Club, January 4, 1941-December 27, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Fox Films, January 2, 1942-December 31, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Fox News, January 4, 1942-December 27, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Fox Mickey Mouse Club, January 1, 1942-December 26, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Fox Films, January 3, 1943-December 31, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Fox News, January 10, 1943-October 19, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Fox Mickey Mouse Club, January 16, 1943-December 31, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Fox Films, January 1, 1944-December 31, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Fox News, January 1, 1944-December 31, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Fox Mickey Mouse Club, January 1, 1944-December 27, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Fox Films, January 1, 1945-December 31, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Fox News, January 2, 1945-December 27, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Fox Mickey Mouse Club, February 3, 1945-December 29, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Fox Films, January 1, 1946-December 31, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Fox News, January 4, 1946-December 19, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Fox Mickey Mouse Club, January 5, 1946-December 21, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Fox Films, January 1, 1947-December 31, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Fox News, January 9, 1947-December 14, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Fox Mickey Mouse Club, February 22, 1947-December 27, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Fox Films, January 1, 1948-December 31, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Fox News, May 19, 1948-December 31, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Fox Mickey Mouse Club, January 3, 1948-December 31, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Fox Films, January 1, 1949-February 28, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Fox Films, March 1, 1949-April 30, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Fox Films, May 1, 1949-June 30, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Fox Films, July 1, 1949-August 31, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Fox Films, September 1, 1949-October 31, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Fox Films, November 1, 1949-December 31, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Fox News, January 1, 1949-December 31, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Fox Mickey Mouse Club, January 8, 1949-December 31, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Fox Index, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Fox Films, January 1, 1950-February 28, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Fox Films, March 1, 1950-April 30, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Fox Films, May 1, 1950-June 30, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Fox Films, July 1, 1950-August 31, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Fox Films, September 1, 1950-October 31, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Fox Films, November 1, 1950-December 31, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Fox News, January 23, 1950-December 20, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Fox Mickey Mouse Club, January 7, 1950-December 30, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Fox Index, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Fox Films, January 1, 1951-December 31, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Fox News, January 7, 1951-October 4, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Fox Mickey Mouse Club, January 6, 1951-December 29, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Fox Films, January 1, 1952-December 31, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Fox News, January 16, 1952-December 21, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Fox Mickey Mouse Club, January 12, 1952-December 27, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Fox Films, January 1, 1953-December 31, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Fox News, January 11, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Fox Films, January 1, 1954-December 24, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Fox News, January 3, 1954-October 30, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Fox Mickey Mouse Club, January 9, 1954-December 31, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Fox Films, January 13, 1955-December 31, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Fox News, April 8, 1955-November 11, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Fox Mickey Mouse Club, January 8, 1955-December 31, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Fox Films, January 1, 1956-December 31, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Fox News, January 1, 1956-December 12, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Fox Mickey Mouse Club, January 7, 1956-December 29, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Fox remodeleing, closing, 1956, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Fox Films, January 3, 1957-December 31, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Fox News, January 23, 1957-December 20, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Fox Mickey Mouse Club, January 12, 1957-December 28, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Fox Films, January 15, 1958-December 31, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Fox News, February 22, 1958-December 27, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Fox Mickey Mouse Club, January 4, 1958-December 27, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Fox Films, January 10, 1959-December 20, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Fox News, January 11, 1959-December 26, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Fox Mickey Mouse Club, January 3, 1959-December 19, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Fox Films, January 1, 1960-December 31, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Fox Films, January 4, 1961-December 22, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Fox News, January 17, 1961-December 20, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Fox Mickey Mouse Club, January 7, 1961-December 30, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Fox Films, January 1, 1962-December 21, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Fox Mickey Mouse Club, January 6, 1962-November 17, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Fox Films, January 9, 1963-December 31, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Fox News, January 18, 1963-December 25, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Fox Films, January 1, 1964-December 31, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Fox Films, January 1, 1965-December 25, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Fox Films, January 2, 1966-December 25, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Fox Mickey Mouse Club, December 27, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Fox Films, January 1, 1967-December 20, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Fox News, February 2, 1967-December 24, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Fox Mickey Mouse Club, February 17, 1967-October 20, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Fox Films, January 7, 1968-December 27, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Fox News, February 4, 1968-September 11, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Fox Films, January 22, 1969-December 25, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Fox Films, January 4, 1970-December 25, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Fox Films, January 1, 1971-December 24, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Fox Films, January 1, 1972-December 22, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Fox News, February 23, 1972-June 1, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Fox Films, January 1, 1973-December 26, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Fox News, January 2, 1973-October 14, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Fox Films, January 2, 1974-June 12, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Fox News, January 14, 1974-June 18, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Fox News, June 1, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Fox News, January 29, 1981-May 11, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Fox News, September, 2000-October 30, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Fox News, January 10, 2002-December, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Fox News, July 31, 2003-November 22, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Fox News, February 5, 2004-November 9, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Fox News, January 14, 2005-December 28, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Fox News, January 1, 2006-September 15, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Fox News, June 3, 2008-February 18, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Series II: Subject files, 1883-2004; (bulk 1930-1945)
  Contains subject files collected and maintained by various volunteers arranged alphabetically. Files cover many individual research projects conducted by Bill Buehler and the Memories Project. Many projects did not get completed while others were never researched. A majority of this series covers well-known personalities of the time that performed at, or were associated with, the Fox Theater. Other, more topical and miscellaneous files are also included.
  - Arizona Historical Society research files, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Douglas Grand Theater, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Film in Arizona, Arizona Film Commission, circa 2000 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Fox, Old Star building, 1883-1901, 1930 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Fox Ad, Tucson Gun Club Brochure, 1932 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Fox managers, April 10, 1930-May 3, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Fox organ, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Fox Personalities, Apache Dance Team AKA "Dooley's Indians", 1931, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Fox Personalities, Arizona Wranglers, March 18, 1931 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Fox Personalities, Demetrio Hamilton, circa 1955 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Fox Personalities, Doctor Alfonso Tirado, November 21, 1931 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Fox Personalities, Doctor William James Mayo, 1933-1940 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Fox Personalities, Eddie Tamblyn, January 18, 1934-January 20, 1934 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Fox Personalities, Fred McSpadden, manager, 1930-1959 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Fox Personalities, Harry Encimas and the San Xavier Band, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Fox Personalities, Hurlstone Fairchild, 1931, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Fox Personalities, Jessica Dragonette, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Fox Personalities, J.L. "Dooley" Bockman, April 10, 1930-November 9, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Fox Personalities, Major Bowes Amateur Hour, March 13, 1936 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Fox Personalities, Mills Brothers, 1935 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Fox Personalities, Monty Montana, February 23, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Fox Personalities, Pepper Carpenter, January 16, 1931 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Fox Personalities, Rodeo -- Montana, Knight, and Holcomb, 1936-1941 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Fox photo files, circa 1931-1958 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Fox restoration, renovations, 1982-2006 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Fox special materials, 1929-1954, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Fox Star origins, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Friends of the Fox, 1930-1958 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - The Marquee, Fox Tucson Theatre Foundation, 2000-2004 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Photographs, Fox events, 1929-1934 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Reenactment of stage performances, 1930-1942 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Religion at the Fox, 1930-1933 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - University of Arizona link, 1930-1945 (Box 6, Folder 62)
- Series III: Oral History files, 1915-2006
  Contains files associated with the oral history interviews that were conducted by the Memories Project. Many photos and other ephemera were donated by interview subjects. Logs include specifications such as tape number, interest and release forms, abstracts of memories shared, as well as scheduling. Details such as the strategies employed while interviewing subjects, and planning of the project itself, which are administrative in nature, are included as well.
  - Fox Theatre property papers, 1937, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Gus Mazon photo album, circa 1933, 1940, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Interest and Release forms, circa 2000-2006 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Interview log (1 of 2), 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Interview log (2 of 2), 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Interview strategies, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Loose photos, circa 1915, 1923, 1927, 1946, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Photo binder (1 of 2), 1933-2003 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Photo binder (2 of 2), 1933-2003 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Project planning, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Restoration log, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Barleycorn interview, August 5, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Written memories, 2000-2005 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Series IV: Oral History media, 2001-2008
  Contains oral history video interviews conducted by the Memories Project. Restoration work and efforts at the Fox Theater are also documented. Recorded materials are in VHS, tape cassette, and Mini DV formats and comprise about 70 hours and approximately 100 interviews. These materials are arranged by tape number and type.
  - VHS Tape, No. 1, Weese, Torres, Barleycorn, circa 2001 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - VHS Tape, Windows to the Past, Dolores Deleon-Tickner, circa 2001 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - VHS Tape, Demo Tape, Pat Irvine and Janet Galleger, circa 2001 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Video interview transcripts, January 4, 2001-January 23, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Don Story Tape, Black, Jones, Danahue, Grossetta, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Jim Drachman CD recording, "Sentimental Journey", undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - VHS Tape, No. 10 and No. 11, Roy Drachman, Catalinas in Winter, Roy Drachman (2nd half), Hank Oyama and Ruben Moreno, M. Carson, circa 2002 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - VHS Tape, No. 25, C. Farrell, Will Rogers, B. McLaughlin, A. Sterrett, circa 2002 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Tape No. 1, Tom Weese, Alva Torres, Virginia Barleycorn, circa 2001 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Tape No. 2, Virginia Barleycorn, Willie Fears, Bertha Sanchez, circa 2001 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Tape No. 3, Teresa and John Kanello, Bud Simons, Sunny Solot, circa 2001 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Tape No. 4, Mary Wong, Tom Wilson, Morgan Maxwell, Edith Auslander, circa 2001 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Tape No. 5, Bloom Family, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Tape No. 6, Edwards, Fox Theater manager, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Tape No. 7, Probesco, Wynonna Mahan, Rudy Reuser, J. Whitten, 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Tape No. 8, Jim Drachman, Felix Morelos, William Stamper, Irene Schmid, Arnend Franks, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Tape No. 9, Joann and Spyro Diamos, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Tape No. 10, Roy Drachman, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Tape No. 11, Catalina Sunset, Roy Drachman, Henry Oyama and Ruben Moreno, M. Carson, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Tape No. 12, Mary Wong, Thompson Hoyt, H. Ackerman, G. and M. Hawke, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Tape No. 13, Enue Clark, 2nd with Tommy Weese, Mark Hart, 2nd with Thompson Hoyt, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Tape No. 14, Art Brown, Tommy Smith, Charles Johnson, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Tape No. 15, J.D. Everett, Lou and Bob Biddle, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Tape No. 16, Julietta Portillo, J. Corkron, M. Workman, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Tape No. 17, Clarke Rasche, Clyde Griffin, Mary Schneider, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Tape No. 17B, C. Twitchell, D. Dowell, G. Guendelsbengen, J. Gibson, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Tape No. 18, Helen Hensler, Joan Schell, Gloria Mazeika, E. Petrie, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Tape No. 19, L. Watkins, M.E. Maytorena and Evelyn Douglas, Kari Slayer, 'Emi' Rogers, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Tape No. 20, B. Osuna, photos from Lauerman, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Tape No. 21, B. Osuna, J. Wade, H. Simms, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Tape No. 22, P. Irvine and J. Gallager, G. Codd, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Tape No. 23, Bill Foltz, Virginia Gallardo, Gloria Scates, 2001, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Tape No. 24, Betty Russell, H. Myers, A. Silvas, D. Ortega, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Tape No. 25, C. Farrell, B. McLaughlin, A. Sterrelt, 2001, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Tape No. 26, Ben Glover, T. Workman, B. Ortiz, P. Monier, 2001, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Tape No. 27, Pat Pettis, H. Adamson, J. Arnold, J. Heath, 2001, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Tape No. 28, Fred McAnich, Louis Yslas, Steven Jr. and Sr., 2002 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Tape No. 29, Bob Ranes, Harry Moore, R.M. Franko, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Tape No. 30, Katie Ousenberry, M. Garigan, John Hanson, R. Reason, 2002, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Tape No. 31, C. Steger, C. Steger, Gus Mazon, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Tape No. 32, Alex Jacome, Bill Saunders, Joe Martinez, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Tape No. 33, P. and R. Quinteros, Jim DeCook, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Tape No. 34, Gladys Klingenberg, Cubby Stevens, Kathy and Ron Oberholtzer, 2004, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Tape No. 35, Andy Solano, Cynthia Hale, Galioto and Martinez, A. Pain, 2003, 2004, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Tape No. 36, Amphi Reunion, Kate Dobson, 2003, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Tape No. 37, THS Reunion, R. Trimble, 2003, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Tape No. 38, Ted Klassen, Living in the Fox, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Tape No. 39, W. and J. Holdberg, Tom Berringer, Higginsons, 2004, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Tape No. 40, Mike Chinak, Dee Smyth, D. Searles, D. McNerney, 2005, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Tape No. 41, Thor Hanson, Don Pitt, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Tape No. 42, J. and R. Jacome, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Tape No. 43, John McSpadden shares life of his dad, Fred, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Fox Restoration Tape No. 1, Chandelier, Work Day, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 1)